<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="recipe_titles">
        <item>Spaghetti</item>
        <item>Meatballs</item>
        <item>Mofongo</item>
        <item>Salmon Avocado</item>
        <item>Lemon Chicken Sandwich</item>
        <item>Tacos</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_info">
        <item>Incredibly tasty Italian dish.</item>
        <item>One of the best things you can try</item>
        <item>Excellent stuff. 10/10</item>
        <item>Great sushi, best ingredients</item>
        <item>Lemon? Check. Chicken? Check. Awesome? Check</item>
        <item>Viva Mexico!</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="recipe_images">
        <item>@drawable/img_spaguetti</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_meatballs</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mofongo</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_salmon_avocado</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chicken_sandwich</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_tacos</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_generic_recipe</item> <!--The generic recipe needs to be the last item on the list !-->
    </array>

    <string-array name="recipe_descriptions">
        <item name="spaghetti">\n
            \u2022 1 pound ground beef \n
            \u2022 1 large onion, chopped \n
            \u2022 2 garlic cloves, minced \n
            \u2022 1 (8-ounce) can tomato sauce \n
            \u2022 3 cups tomato juice \n
            \u2022 1 cup water \n
            \u2022 1 teaspoon salt \n
            \u2022 1 teaspoon sugar \n
            \u2022 2 to 3 teaspoons chi li powder \n
            \u2022 1 teaspoon dried oregano \n
            \u2022 Dash of pepper \n
            \u2022 1 (7-ounce) package spaghetti \n
            \u2022 uncooked Grated Parmesan cheese \n
            \u2022 Garnish: fresh Italian parsley sprigs
            \n \n Step 1 \n
            \n Cook first 3 ingredients in a Dutch oven, stirring until beef crumbles and is no longer pink; drain well.
            \n Return beef mixture to pan. Stir in tomato sauce and next 8 ingredients; bring to a boil.
            \n Cover, reduce heat, and simmer, stirring often, 30 minutes.
            \n \n Step 2 \n
            \n Add pasta; cover and simmer, stirring often, 20 minutes or until pasta is tender.
            \n Serve with cheese, and garnish, if desired.
        </item>
        <item name="meatballs">\n
            \u2022 2 teaspoons olive oil \n
            \u2022 1 medium onion, chopped \n
            \u2022 3 garlic cloves, minced \n
            \u2022 3/4 cup seasoned bread crumbs \n
            \u2022 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese \n
            \u2022 2 large Nellie’s Free Range Eggs, lightly beaten \n
            \u2022 1 teaspoon each dried basil, oregano and parsley flakes \n
            \u2022 3/4 teaspoon salt \n
            \u2022 1 pound lean ground turkey \n
            \u2022 1 pound lean ground beef (90% lean) \n
            \u2022 Hot cooked pasta and pasta sauce, optional
            \n \n [Preheat oven to 375°. In a small skillet, heat oil over medium-high heat.
            \n \n Add onion; cook and stir 3-4 minutes or until tender.]
            \n \n Add garlic; cook 1 minute longer. Cool slightly.
            \n \n In a large bowl, combine bread crumbs, cheese, eggs, seasonings and onion mixture.
            \n \n Add turkey and beef; mix lightly but thoroughly. Shape into 1-1/2-in. balls.
            \n \n Place meatballs on a rack coated with cooking spray in a 15x10x1-in. baking pan.
            \n \n Bake 18-22 minutes or until lightly browned and cooked through. If desired, serve with pasta and pasta sauce.</item>
        <item name="mofongo"> \n
            \u2022 3 garlic cloves, \n
            \u2022 minced 3/4 ounce \n
            \u2022 fried pork rinds, \n
            \u2022 crushed (1/2 packed cup) \n
            \u2022 1/2 cup extra-virgin olive oil Vegetable oil for frying 2 large green plantains (about 12 ounces each), \n
            \u2022 peeled and cut into 1-inch-thick rounds \n
            \u2022 Salt \n
            \u2022 Freshly ground pepper \n
            \u2022 1 pound medium shrimp, shelled and deveined \n
            \u2022 1/2 cup dry white wine
            \n \n Step 1 \n
            \n In a bowl, combine two-thirds of the minced garlic cloves with the pork rinds and 1 tablespoon of the olive oil and mash to combine.
            \n \n Step 2 \n
            \n In a large saucepan, heat 1 inch of vegetable oil to 350°.
            \n Add the plantains and fry, keeping the oil at about 300°, until very tender, but not browned, 15 minutes.
            \n Drain and transfer the plantains to a large bowl. Using a potato masher, mash the plantains to a coarse puree with 1 tablespoon of the olive oil.
            \n Add the garlic–pork rind mixture and mash until evenly combined. Season the mofongo with salt and pepper; keep warm.
            \n \n Step 3 \n
            \n In a large skillet, heat the remaining 1/4 cup plus 2 tablespoons of olive oil until shimmering.
            \n Add the shrimp and remaining garlic, season with salt and pepper and cook over high heat, stirring occasionally, until curled, about 2 minutes.
            \n Add the wine and boil until nearly evaporated and the shrimp are cooked through, about 2 minutes longer.
            \n \n Step 4 \n
            \n Spoon the mofongo into bowls and top with the shrimp. Serve right away.
        </item>
        <item name="salmon"> \n
            \u2022 1 avocado, pitted, peeled, and sliced thinly \n
            \u2022 1 tablespoon seasoned rice vinegar or lemon juice \n
            \u2022 4 sheets nori \n
            \u2022 About 3 cups cooked and cooled Sushi Rice (recipe link in intro) \n
            \u2022 8 ounces sashimi-grade salmon, cut into ½-inch strips \n
            \u2022 Pickled ginger \n
            \u2022 Wasabi \n
            \u2022 Soy sauce
            \n \n Step 1 \n
            \n Sprinkle the avocado with vinegar to prevent browning while you work.
            \n \n Step 2 \n
            \n Place a bamboo sushi mat on a flat work surface with the slats running horizontally.
            \n Lay a piece of plastic wrap over the bamboo mat. \n Place a sheet of nori on the plastic wrap, shiny side down.
            \n \n Step 3 \n
            \n With wet hands, spread about 3/4 cup of the rice over the surface of the nori, leaving about a 1/2-inch uncovered on the furthest edge.
            \n Press and spread the rice down firmly but gently, wetting your hands again if needed to prevent sticking.
            \n \n Step 4 \n
            \n Set the salmon pieces end-to-end across the center of the rice. Top the salmon with a few slices of avocado (it’s okay if they overlap a bit).
            \n Begin rolling the edge of the bamboo closest to you over the salmon line, using the mat to press down on the sushi roll firmly but gently.
            \n When you get to the raw edge of nori, use your finger to lightly wet the nori, then continue to roll up so it’s sealed.
            \n The nori should stick to itself when the roll is complete.
            \n \n Step 5 \n
            \n Remove the plastic wrap and set the roll aside, covering with a damp cloth while you work on the remaining rolls.
            \n Repeat until all of the rice has been used.
            \n \n Step 6 \n
            \n Cut each roll in half, and then half again, and then half again, so each roll is cut into 8 even pieces.
            \n Serve with pickled ginger, wasabi, and soy sauce.
        </item>
        <item name="sandwich"> \n
            \u2022 4 boneless skinless chicken breasts (6-8 oz each) \n
            \u2022 Lemon pepper seasoning \n
            \u2022 8 slices pepper bacon \n
            \u2022 4 slices cheddar cheese (or your favorite cheese) \n
            \u2022 4 sandwich buns \n
            \u2022 Mayonnaise (or dressing of your choice) \n
            \u2022 Tomatoes, slices (optional) \n
            \u2022 4 lettuce leaves (optional) \n
            \u2022 sliced onion (optional)
            \n \n On a cutting board, pound the chicken breasts briefly with a mallet to flatten the thick parts so they\'ll cook more evenly.
            \n \n Cut each strip of bacon in half.
            \n Arrange strips in a large (12\") skillet and cook over medium heat until it reaches your desired crispness.
            \n Remove cooked bacon from skillet and put on paper towels to absorb excess grease.
            \n \n Pour off all but approximately 1 tablespoon of the bacon grease. (you can pour it all off and then add back 1 TB - you decide!).
            \n \n Heat skillet again, over medium-low to medium heat.
            \n \n Liberally sprinkle both sides of the chicken breasts with lemon pepper.
            \n When the skillet is hot, place all 4 chicken breasts in it.
            \n Cook approximately 4 minutes on one side.
            \n \n Flip the chicken breasts over. Arrange the bacon slices on top.
            \n Then place sliced cheese on top of the bacon.
            \n \n Cover the skillet and cook for about another 4 minutes. The cheese should be well-melted.
            \n To test doneness, poke the fattest part of a breast with a sharp knife - you shouldn\'t see any pink meat left in the middle.
            \n \n Dress your bun with mayonnaise, a dijon/mayonnaise combo, or ranch dressing.
            \n Put chicken on bun.
            \n It tastes great without veggies, but you can also add leafy lettuce, sliced tomato, and sliced onion.
        </item>
        <item> \n
            \u2022 1 lb lean ground beef \n
            \u2022 1 medium onion, chopped \n
            \u2022 1 teaspoon chili powder \n
            \u2022 1/2 teaspoon salt \n
            \u2022 1/2 teaspoon garlic powder \n
            \u2022 1 can (8 oz) tomato sauce \n
            \u2022 12 Old El Paso™ crunchy taco shells  \n
            \u2022 1 1/2 cups shredded Cheddar cheese (6 oz)  \n
            \u2022 2 cups shredded lettuce \n
            \u2022 2 medium tomatoes, chopped \n
            \u2022 3/4 cup Old El Paso™ Thick \'n Chunky salsa \n
            \u2022 3/4 cup sour cream, if desired.
            \n \n Step 1 \n
            \n Heat oven to 250°F.
            \n In large skillet, brown ground beef and onion over medium heat for 8 to 10 minutes or until beef is thoroughly cooked, stirring frequently. Drain.
            \n \n Step 2 \n
            \n Stir in chili powder, salt, garlic powder and tomato sauce.
            \n Reduce heat to low; cover and simmer 10 minutes.
            \n \n Step 3 \n
            \n Meanwhile, place taco shells on ungreased cookie sheet.
            \n Heat at 250°F. for 5 minutes.
            \n \n Step 4 \n
            \n To assemble tacos, layer beef mixture, cheese, lettuce and tomatoes in each taco shell.
            \n Serve with salsa; top with sour cream.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_links">
        <item>https://www.southernliving.com/recipes/all-in-one-spaghetti-recipe</item>
        <item>https://www.tasteofhome.com/recipes/great-grandma-s-italian-meatballs/</item>
        <item>https://www.foodandwine.com/recipes/mofongo-with-shrimp</item>
        <item>https://www.chowhound.com/recipes/salmon-avocado-maki-31555</item>
        <item>https://www.geniuskitchen.com/recipe/lemon-pepper-bacon-chicken-sandwich-pioneer-woman-329678</item>
        <item>https://www.pillsbury.com/recipes/ground-beef-tacos/7217b5cb-5bdc-4458-a6e4-844a39188b9c</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>